<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipes Directory</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_info">Information</string>
    <string name="action_uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="chococake_recipe">1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\n
                                    2. Grease and flour two nine inch round pans.\n\n
                                    3. Bake 30 to 35 minutes in the preheated oven, until the cake tests done with a toothpick.\n\n
                                    4. Cool in the pans for 10 minutes, then remove to a wire rack to cool completely.In a large bowl, stir together the sugar, flour, cocoa, baking powder, baking soda and salt.\n\n
                                    5. Add the eggs, milk, oil and vanilla, mix for 2 minutes on medium speed of mixer. Stir in the boiling water last. Batter will be thin. Pour evenly into the prepared pans.</string>
    <string name="redvelvet_recipe">1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\n
                                    2. Grease two 9-inch round pans.Beat shortening and 1 1/2 cups sugar until very light and fluffy.\n\n
                                    3. Add eggs and beat well.Make a paste of cocoa and red food coloring; add to creamed mixture. Mix salt, 1 teaspoon vanilla, and buttermilk together.\n\n
                                    4. Add the flour to the batter, alternating with the buttermilk mixture, mixing just until incorporated. Mix soda and vinegar and gently fold into cake batter.Pour batter into prepared pans.\n\n
                                    5. Bake in preheated oven until a tester inserted into the cake comes out clean, about 30 minutes. Cool cakes completely on wire rack.</string>
    <string name="carrotcake_recipe">1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\n
                                     2. Grease a 9x13 inch baking pan. Set aside.In a large bowl, mix together sugar, oil, eggs, vanilla, and buttermilk. Stir in carrots, coconut, vanilla, and pineapple.\n\n
                                     3. In a separate bowl, combine flour, baking soda, cinnamon, and salt; gently stir into carrot mixture. Stir in chopped nuts. Spread batter into prepared pan.\n\n
                                     4. Bake for 55 minutes or until toothpick inserted into cake comes out clean. Remove from oven, and set aside to cool.\n\n
                                     5. In a medium mixing bowl, combine butter or margarine, cream cheese, vanilla, and confectioners sugar. Blend until creamy. Frost cake while still in the pan.</string>
    <string name="raspberrycake_recipe">1. In a saucepan, combine raspberries, 2 tablespoons sugar, cornstarch, and water.\n\n
                                        2. Bring to boil, and continue boiling 5 minutes, or until sauce is thick. Strain sauce through a mesh strainer to remove seeds.\n\n
                                        3. Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). In a metal bowl over a pan of simmering water, melt white chocolate chips with half-and-half, stirring occasionally until smooth.\n\n
                                        4. In a large bowl, mix together cream cheese and 1/2 cup sugar until smooth. Beat in eggs one at a time. Blend in vanilla and melted white chocolate. Pour half of batter over crust. Spoon 3 tablespoons raspberry sauce over batter.\n\n
                                        5. Pour remaining cheesecake batter into pan, and again spoon 3 tablespoons raspberry sauce over the top.Bake for 55 to 60 minutes, or until filling is set. Cool, cover with plastic wrap, and refrigerate for 8 hours before removing from pan.\n\n
                                        6. Serve with remaining raspberry sauce.</string>
    <string name="walnutcake_recipe">1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\n
                                     2. Grease and flour a 9x13 inch pan. Sift together the flour, baking soda, cinnamon and salt. Set aside.\n\n
                                     3. Combine the apples and the white sugar; set aside. In a large bowl, mix together the brown sugar, oil, eggs and vanilla.\n\n
                                     4. Stir in the apple mixture, then the flour mixture. Fold in the walnuts.Pour batter into prepared pan. \n\n
                                     5. Bake in the preheated oven for 45 minutes, or until a toothpick inserted into the center of the cake comes out clean. Allow to cool.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_recipe">1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\n
                                     2. Grease a 9 inch spring form pan. In a medium bowl, mix graham cracker crumbs with melted butter. Press onto bottom of spring form pan.\n\n
                                     3. In a large bowl, mix cream cheese with sugar until smooth. Blend in milk, and then mix in the eggs one at a time, mixing just enough to incorporate.\n\n
                                     4. Mix in sour cream, vanilla and flour until smooth. Pour filling into prepared crust. Bake in preheated oven for 1 hour. Turn the oven off, and let cake cool in oven with the door closed for 5 to 6 hours; this prevents cracking.\n\n
                                     5. Chill in refrigerator until serving.</string>
    <string name="eclaircake_recipe">1. In a medium bowl, thoroughly blend the pudding mix, whipped topping, and milk.\n\n
                                     2. Arrange a single layer of graham cracker squares in the bottom of a 13x9 inch baking pan.\n\n
                                     3. Evenly spread half of the pudding mixture over the crackers. Top with another layer of crackers and the remaining pudding mixture. Top with a final layer of graham crackers. \n\n
                                     4. Spread the frosting over the whole cake up to the edges of the pan. Cover, and chill at least 4 hours before serving.</string>

    <string name="cakeRecpies_info"> RecipesList app has the best cake recipes prepared by the famous Indian baker Vikram Suresh.\n\n Easy to follow steps will make your baking a pleasure.</string>

</resources>
